Finding Aid for the Ernest Fleischmann Papers LSC.2293
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Writings and personal materials, 1960-2010
  - Cards, 1998-2010 (Box 88, Folder 10, Box 90, Folder 9, Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Certificates, 1990s-2000s (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Chopin Piano Concerto No. 1, undated (Box 102)
    Two 1/4 inch audiotapes. Tape one contains movements 1-2; tape two contains movement 3.
  - Cleveland speech, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 4, Box 92, Folder 4-5)
  - Commemorative sign, 1990s (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, notes, lectures, speeches, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Datebooks, 1969-2009 (Box 74-83)
  - Donations, 1996-2000 (Box 90, Folder 2, 6)
  - "D' You Think It Worked?", undated (Box 85, Folder 1-2, Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dual citizenship, nationality, and immigration, 1942-2010 (Box 8, Folder 3, Box 5, Folder 6, Box 15, Folder 5, Box 3)
  - Jessica Fleischmann, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Stephanie Fleischmann, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Honors, 1999-2001 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Lectures and speeches, 1980-2003 (Box 93, Folder 3, Box 87, Folder 9-11)
  - Memoirs, 2003-2008 (Box 89, Folder 1, Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Press, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Tributes, 1991-1998 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Writings and talks, circa 2003 (Box 87, Folder 3, Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Financial documents, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Five books, 1966-1994 (Box 104)
  - Fleischmann Arts: personal correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 86, Folder 5-6)
  - Fleischmann biography, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Fleischmann contributions, 1998-2003 (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
  - Fleischmann donations, 1992-1993 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Fleischmann's 80th birthday, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Fleischmann, Stephanie and Mark, 2002-2007 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Getty Talk, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Historic clippings, 1986-2008 (Box 73, Folder 7, Box 11, Folder 4, Box 99)
  - Holiday cards and gift lists, 2002-2007 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - LA Weekly press, 2007 (Box 99)
  - LAPA: Fleischmann photographs, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Letterhead, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic scrapbook, 1998 (Box 100)
  - Los Angeles Times: obituary, 2010 (Box 99)
  - Los Angeles Times: retirement, 1998 (Box 99)
  - New York Herald Tribune: commemorative birthday edition, 1984 (Box 101)
  - Notebooks, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Notes and writings, circa 1980s (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Oral History, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Personal correspondence and clippings, 1985-2010 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 11, Folder 6, Box 84, Folder 2-3, Box 12, Folder 3, Box 10, Folder 9, Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Personal correspondence, 1971-2010 (Box 90, Folder 7, Box 86, Folder 7-8, Folder 1-4, 7-8, Box 84, Folder 4-9, Box 7, Folder 10, Box 85, Folder 4-5, Box 89, Folder 3,5, 8)
  - Personal correspondence: medical, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photograph: Elizabeth Baker, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Photographs, 1960s-2000s; 1988-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1-4, Box 101, Folder 1, Box 89, Folder 9)
    Primarily 8 x 10 black and white photographs, some taken by Los Angeles philanthropist and photographer, Betty Freeman.
  - RPS lecture and related documents, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 2, Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Talks, papers, and lectures, circa 1985-1999 (Box 87, Folder 6, 8)
  - "The Orchestra Is Dead. Long Live The Community of Musicians.", 1987 May 16 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - The Stars Come Out for Ernest Fleischmann, 1998 June 24 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - "The Tapes" draft, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Tokyo Orchestra Summit talk, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Travel: accident in Frankfurt, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Travel: general, 1978-1998 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Travel: Rome, 1996-1997 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Travel: South Africa, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - "Who runs our orchestras...and who should?", 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)